fincen.gov 2013-06-06

# Privacy & Security

## Welcome

Thank you for visiting the Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN) website and reviewing our privacy policy. This website is provided as a public service and is considered public information, which may be distributed or copied in accordance with applicable law. Use of appropriate byline/photo/image credits is requested.

## Privacy Notice

FinCEN's privacy policy is clear: FinCEN respects your privacy. We will collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us.

When you visit our site, for site management purposes, we collect information about your visit on an anonymous, aggregate basis. The information collected includes: the name of the domain from which you accessed the Internet; the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site; and the date and time you accessed our site. The U.S. Department of the Treasury and FinCEN use this information to monitor site security, measure site activity, and to develop ideas for improving site performance. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits.           

We will not collect information which identifies you (name, email address, Social Security number, or other unique identifiers) when you visit our site, unless you voluntarily choose to provide such information to us in your e-mail or through other means such as an on-line form. In addition, if you are commenting on proposed rulemakings or other regulatory actions, your comment will be available to the general public. Also, if you send us information which identifies you in an electronic message, that information may be forwarded to other Government employees and agencies to more fully respond to your correspondence.            

Privacy Impact Assessments (PIAs) are performed on computer systems and applications in order to evaluate any risks these systems may pose to personally identifiable information. FinCEN’s PIAs can be accessed via the PIA site: http://www.fincen.gov/foia/pia.html

## Security Notice

Unauthorized attempts to upload information and/or change information on these web sites are strictly prohibited and are subject to criminal prosecution. 

**Procedures for Implementation of the Information Quality Law**

If you have any questions or comments about the information presented here, please forward them to [**webmaster@fincen.gov**](mailto:webmaster@fincen.gov)
